The fury no one saw coming...
Meteor Storm is a science fiction, adventure, tv
movie film directed by Tibor Takács.
San Francisco becomes a target for waves of destructive meteors
after a rogue comet orbits around the earth...
For astronomer, Michelle Young, what was meant to be a once-in-a-lifetime celestial event, soon turns into her worst
nightmare as thousands of meteors break the surface of the atmosphere and bombard the city of San Francisco.
Tom, played by Michael Trucco.
Michelle, played by Kari Matchett.
Jason Young, played by Brett Dier.
Kyle Pember, played by Eric Johnson.
Général Brock, played by Kevin McNulty.
Lena, played by Lara Gilchrist.
Brett Jordan Dier (; born February 14, 1990) is a Canadian actor.
He is best known for his role as Michael Cordero Jr.
on Jane the Virgin.
He is also known for his recurring roles on the
Canadian TV shows Bomb Girls and The L.A.
Complex, and for his main role as "C.B." on the ABC sitcom Schooled.
The tone is thought_provoking.